<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">BioComp</string>

    <string name="message_1">Insert birthday date!</string>
    <string name="commento">With this score you have </string>
    <string name="fisico_1">and a low physical attraction.</string>
    <string name="fisico_2">and a warm physical attraction.</string>
    <string name="fisico_3">and a middle physical attraction.</string>
    <string name="fisico_4">and a strong physical attraction.</string>
    <string name="emotivo_1">a low emotional involvement, </string>
    <string name="emotivo_2">a little emotional involvement, </string>
    <string name="emotivo_3">a middle emotional involvement, </string>
    <string name="emotivo_4">a strong emotional involvement, </string>
    <string name="intellettuale_1">a very low intellectual compatibility, </string>
    <string name="intellettuale_2">a low intellectual compatibility, </string>
    <string name="intellettuale_3">a middle intellectual compatibility, </string>
    <string name="intellettuale_4">an huge intellectual compatibility, </string>
    <string name="fisico">Physical</string>
    <string name="emotivo">Emotional</string>
    <string name="intellettuale">Intellectual</string>
    <string name="calculate_biocomp">Calculate Bio Compatibility</string>
    <string name="button_2">Reset</string>
    <string name="date">mm/dd/yyyy</string>

    <string name="take_screenshot">Take screenshot</string>
    <string name="n_a">Screenshot interface not (yet) available.</string>
    <string name="native_n_a">Native service not found.</string>
    <string name="screenshot_error">Error while taking screenshot.</string>
    <string name="screenshot_ok">Screenshot taken successfully.</string>
    <string name="add_a_new_date">Add a new Date</string>

    <string name="load_date">Load Date</string>
    <string name="intellectual">Intellectual</string>
    <string name="emotional">Emotional</string>
    <string name="physical">Physical</string>
    <string name="choose_a_date">Choose date</string>
    <string name="calculate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="share_on_facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="select_a_new_date">New Date</string>
    <string name="infos">Infos</string>
    <string name="other_apps">Other Apps</string>
    <string name="twitter">Twitter</string>
    <string name="datelist">Date List</string>
    <string name="intro_biocomp">BioComp is an app that calculates the compatibility between people through the theory of biorhythms.</string>

    <string name="calculate_compatibility">Calculate Compatibility</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_biocomp">Welcome to BioComp</string>
    <string name="enter_new_profile">Enter New Profile</string>
    <string name="your_date_list">Your List of Dates</string>
    <string name="choose_date">Choose date</string>
    <string name="our_other_apps">Our Other Apps</string>
    <string name="load_or_new">Load or Create Date</string>

    <string name="banner">ca-app-pub-1505207846260374/5186273936</string>
    <string name="prova_banner">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>

    <string name="save_profile">Save profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_date_list">DateList</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">1637657219830501</string>

    <string name="descr">Hello! for calculate Bio Compatibility, choose the avatars and birth dates.</string>

    <string name="theory">Theory Of Biorhythms</string>
    <string name="other_descr">Download our new app directly from the Google PlayStore.</string>
    <string name="other_infos">For info or any questions, please visit our web site.</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth">Birthdate</string>
    <string name="bio_info">The theory of biorhythms has always devoted great attention also to the problems of affinity between individuals.
        Thanks to these observations it was found that two people whose emotional cycle follows the same fluctuations will have for life the same provision to the feelings, optimism and the same sensitivity.
        Live set of charging and discharging phases and this will lead them to have a great emotional affinity.
        Ne The theory of biorhythms, the ups and downs in the course of a life published in 1959, Hugo Max Gross devotes several chapters to the explanation of the correspondences in marriages and other occasions of relationships between people and develop an evaluation method based on percentages affinity between cycles.
        The method of assessment of compatibility from the consideration that two individuals with two identical cycles have the greatest affinity with a percentage of 100%. As the case of a minor matching occurs in the opposite situation, that is, when the deviation is equal to half of the cycle, giving in this condition a percentage equal to 0%,
        it follows that for each day of discordance the affinity decreases by a percentage equal to 100 / day cycle X 2. the percentage of affinity then 8,70% decrease in the physical cycle of 7.14% in the emotional cycle and 6,06% in the intellectual cycle for each day of the difference between the cycles. Consequently, the lower the percentage, high neno will be the percentage of affinity.
        The calculated cycle by cycle compatibility, can then be defined as a medium that will give us the percentage of overall affinity.
        Generally it is considered a good average percentage higher than 50%. Obviously, a percentage over 70% will tell us that between two people there is a great tune, while a less than 50% puts a serious threat to the possibility of understanding. Physical compatibility is important in the sports team training or work.
        The emotional one for the cartel in a couple, a family or friendships.
        For associations or partnerships based on intellectual activity will be necessary a good intellectual match.
        Obviously this concerns a pure harmony biorhythm: nothing remains that in the presence of important goals or strong reasons these difficulties can be overcome and that, despite a good harmony biorhythm, there are relationship difficulties due to other factors.

    </string>
    <string name="reset_list">reset list</string>
    <string name="choose_descr">Choose the date through these spinners and save.</string>
    <string name="day">Day</string>
    <string name="month">Month</string>
    <string name="year">Year</string>
    <string name="reset">reset</string>
    <string name="result_bio">Result Bio Compatibility</string>
    <string name="insert_register">One of the insert data is wrong!</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirming the date inserted?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="load_new_error">Something went wrong. Couldn\'t load the selected Profile!</string>
    <string name="load_profile">Load a profile from your list of dates, or create a new profile.</string>
    <string name="load_label">Load Date</string>
    <string name="send">Share</string>

</resources>